* Proxy Detection
    * [Proxy Detection
        
        Leading IP Address Intelligence](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/proxy-vpn-tor-detection-service)
    * [Proxy Detection Test
        
        Proxy & VPN IP Lookup](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/free-ip-lookup-proxy-vpn-test)
    * [Tor Detection Test
        
        Identify Tor Connections](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/tor-ip-address-check)
    * [VPN Detection Test
        
        IP Address VPN Checker](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/vpn-ip-address-check)
    * [Bot Detection Test
        
        Identify Bad Bots & Abuse](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/bot-management/bot-detection-check)
    * [Proxy Detection Database
        
        On-Premise IP Address Database](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/proxy-detection-database)
    * [IP Address Blacklist
        
        IP Threat Blocklist](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/ip-block-list-blacklist)
    * [IP Reputation Check
        
        IP Address Fraud Scoring](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/ip-reputation-check)
    * [IP Location Lookup
        
        Pinpoint IP Geolocation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/ip-lookup)
    * [Proxy Detection API
        
        Easy API Documentation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/proxy-detection-api/overview)
* Email Verification
    * [Email Validation
        
        Real-Time Email Verification](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/email-verification)
    * [Email Verifier
        
        Validate Emails & Signals](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/free-email-verifier)
    * [Disposable Email Detection
        
        Block Disposable Emails](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/disposable-email-address-detection)
    * [Email Risk Scoring
        
        Email Threat Analysis](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/fraud-prevention/email-risk-scoring)
    * [Email Fraud Detection
        
        Email Risk Assessment](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/email-reputation/email-address-fraud-prevention)
    * [Email Age Lookup
        
        Email Creation Date Checker](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/email-age-checker)
    * [Email List Cleaning
        
        Improve Email Deliverability](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/email-deliverability/email-list-cleaning)
    * [Domain Reputation
        
        Leading Domain Intelligence](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/domain-reputation)
    * [Domain Age Checker
        
        View Domain Creation Date](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/domain-age-checker)
    * [Email Bounce Checker
        
        Invalid Email Bounce Tester](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/email-bounce-checker)
    * [Reverse Email Lookup
        
        Match Emails to Identities](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/reverse-email-lookup)
    * [Email Spam Test
        
        Test Email Deliverability](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/email-deliverability/email-spam-test-checker)
    * [Email Validation API
        
        Validation API Documentation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/email-validation-api/overview)
* Phone Validation
    * [Phone Validation
        
        Phone Number Intelligence](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/phone-validation)
    * [Phone Number Validator
        
        Phone Number Verification](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/phone-number-validator)
    * [Phone Carrier Lookup
        
        Lookup Phone Service Provider](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/free-carrier-lookup)
    * [Reverse Phone Lookup
        
        Match Phones With Identities](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/reverse-phone-number-lookup)
    * [Phone Number Lookup
        
        Lookup Number Details](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/free-phone-number-lookup)
    * [Phone Number Fraud Scoring
        
        Phone Number Risk Signals](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/fraud-prevention/phone-number-fraud-risk-scoring)
    * [HLR Lookup
        
        Phone Number Connectivity](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/free-hlr-lookup)
    * [Data Appending
        
        Enrich Phone Numbers](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/data-enrichment/data-append)
    * [DNC TCPA List Scrub
        
        Do Not Call List](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/tcpa-compliance/dnc-tcpa-phone-scrub)
    * [Identity Verification
        
        Verify Users & Payments](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/fraud-prevention/identity-verification-api-solution)
    * [Phone Validation API
        
        Verification API Documentation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/phone-number-validation-api/overview)
* Device Fingerprinting
    * [Web Device Fingerprinting
        
        Detect Emulators, Bots, Location Spoofing, & High Risk Behavior Signals](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/device-fingerprinting)
    * [Mobile Fingerprinting SDK
        
        In-App iOS & Android Fingerprinting](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/mobile-device-fingerprinting-sdk)
    * [Device Fingerprint API
        
        Device Fingerprinting Documentation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/device-fingerprint-api/overview)
* Cybersecurity
    * [Malicious URL Scanner
        
        Identify Phishing & Malware](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/threat-feeds/malicious-url-scanner)
    * [File Malware Scanner
        
        File Virus Checker](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/file-malware-scanner)
    * [Data Breach Search
        
        Leaked Data Search Engine](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/data-breach-search-engine)
    * [Leaked Email Checker
        
        Search Leaked Emails](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/data-breach-lookup/leaked-email-checker)
    * [Leaked Password Checker
        
        Search Leaked Passwords](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/data-breach-lookup/password-leak-check)
    * [Leaked Username Checker
        
        Search Compromised Usernames](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/data-breach-lookup/compromised-usernames)
    * [Cyberthreat Intelligence
        
        Identify Advanced Cyberthreats](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/cyberthreat-intelligence-map)
    * [Threat Intelligence Feeds
        
        Real-Time Threat Feeds](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/threat-intelligence-feed-api)
    * [Dark Web Monitoring
        
        Track Dark Web Leaks](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/dark-web-monitoring-api)
    * [URL Scanning API
        
        Link Scanning Documentation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/malicious-url-scanner-api/overview)
    * [Virus Scanning API
        
        File Scanning Documentation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/malware-file-scanner-api/overview)
* Solutions
    * [Ecommerce Fraud
        
        Securely Process Payments](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/ecommerce-fraud-prevention)
    * [Address Verification
        
        Verify Physical Addresses](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/address-verification)
    * [User Validation
        
        Verify Identities with Precision](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/user-application-screening)
    * [Account Takeover (ATO)
        
        Detect Suspicious Logins](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/account-takeover-credential-stuffing-fraud-prevention)
    * [Bot Protection
        
        Detect Automated Bots](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/bot-protection-mitigation)
    * [Chargeback Prevention
        
        Detect Fraudulent Chargebacks](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/chargeback-fraud-prevention)
    * [Prevent Sign Up Fraud
        
        New Account Opening Screening](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/prevent-fake-registration-fraud)
    * [Invalid Traffic (IVT)
        
        Prevent Ad Fraud](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/invalid-traffic-detection)
    * [Fraud Detection API
        
        Risk Scoring API Documentation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/overview)
* Fraud Detection Tools
    * [Bot Detection
        
        Block Bad Bots](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/bot-detection)
    * [Block Proxies
        
        Detect Proxies & Bots](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/block-proxies)
    * [Block Disposable Emails
        
        Prevent Bad Users](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/block-disposable-emails)
    * [Click Fraud Prevention
        
        Monitor Fraudulent Traffic](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/click-fraud-prevention)
    * [Prevent Affiliate Fraud
        
        Affiliate Network Fraud Detection](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/prevent-affiliate-ad-fraud)
    * [Detect Mobile App Fraud
        
        Identify Mobile Emulators & Bots](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/detect-mobile-app-install-fraud)
    * [Fake & Duplicate Accounts
        
        Stop Fake Accounts](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/duplicate-fake-account-detection)
    * [Fraud Fusion™
        
        Fraud Detection Consortium](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/fraud-fusion)
    * [Transaction Risk Scoring API
        
        Verify Payments in Real-Time](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/proxy-detection-api/transaction-scoring)

* [ ]  Proxy Detection
    * [Proxy Detection
        
        Leading IP Address Intelligence](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/proxy-vpn-tor-detection-service)
    * [Proxy Detection Test
        
        Proxy & VPN IP Lookup](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/free-ip-lookup-proxy-vpn-test)
    * [Tor Detection Test
        
        Identify Tor Connections](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/tor-ip-address-check)
    * [VPN Detection Test
        
        IP Address VPN Checker](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/vpn-ip-address-check)
    * [Bot Detection Test
        
        Identify Bad Bots & Abuse](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/bot-management/bot-detection-check)
    * [Proxy Detection Database
        
        On-Premise IP Address Database](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/proxy-detection-database)
    * [IP Address Blacklist
        
        IP Threat Blocklist](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/ip-block-list-blacklist)
    * [IP Reputation Check
        
        IP Address Fraud Scoring](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/ip-reputation-check)
    * [IP Location Lookup
        
        Pinpoint IP Geolocation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/ip-lookup)
    * [Proxy Detection API
        
        Easy API Documentation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/proxy-detection-api/overview)
* [ ]  Email Verification
    * [Email Validation
        
        Real-Time Email Verification](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/email-verification)
    * [Email Verifier
        
        Validate Emails & Signals](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/free-email-verifier)
    * [Disposable Email Detection
        
        Block Disposable Emails](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/disposable-email-address-detection)
    * [Email Risk Scoring
        
        Email Threat Analysis](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/fraud-prevention/email-risk-scoring)
    * [Email Fraud Detection
        
        Email Risk Assessment](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/email-reputation/email-address-fraud-prevention)
    * [Email Age Lookup
        
        Email Creation Date Checker](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/email-age-checker)
    * [Email List Cleaning
        
        Improve Email Deliverability](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/email-deliverability/email-list-cleaning)
    * [Domain Reputation
        
        Leading Domain Intelligence](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/domain-reputation)
    * [Domain Age Checker
        
        View Domain Creation Date](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/domain-age-checker)
    * [Email Bounce Checker
        
        Invalid Email Bounce Tester](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/email-bounce-checker)
    * [Reverse Email Lookup
        
        Match Emails to Identities](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/reverse-email-lookup)
    * [Email Spam Test
        
        Test Email Deliverability](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/email-deliverability/email-spam-test-checker)
    * [Email Validation API
        
        Validation API Documentation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/email-validation-api/overview)
* [ ]  Phone Validation
    * [Phone Validation
        
        Phone Number Intelligence](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/phone-validation)
    * [Phone Number Validator
        
        Phone Number Verification](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/phone-number-validator)
    * [Phone Carrier Lookup
        
        Lookup Phone Service Provider](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/free-carrier-lookup)
    * [Reverse Phone Lookup
        
        Match Phones With Identities](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/reverse-phone-number-lookup)
    * [Phone Number Lookup
        
        Lookup Number Details](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/free-phone-number-lookup)
    * [Phone Number Fraud Scoring
        
        Phone Number Risk Signals](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/fraud-prevention/phone-number-fraud-risk-scoring)
    * [HLR Lookup
        
        Phone Number Connectivity](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/free-hlr-lookup)
    * [Data Appending
        
        Enrich Phone Numbers](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/data-enrichment/data-append)
    * [DNC TCPA List Scrub
        
        Do Not Call List](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/tcpa-compliance/dnc-tcpa-phone-scrub)
    * [Identity Verification
        
        Verify Users & Payments](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/fraud-prevention/identity-verification-api-solution)
    * [Phone Validation API
        
        Verification API Documentation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/phone-number-validation-api/overview)
* [ ]  Device Fingerprinting
    * [Web Device Fingerprinting
        
        Detect Emulators, Bots, Location Spoofing, & High Risk Behavior Signals](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/device-fingerprinting)
    * [Mobile Fingerprinting SDK
        
        In-App iOS & Android Fingerprinting](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/mobile-device-fingerprinting-sdk)
    * [Device Fingerprint API
        
        Device Fingerprinting Documentation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/device-fingerprint-api/overview)
* [ ]  Cybersecurity
    * [Malicious URL Scanner
        
        Identify Phishing & Malware](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/threat-feeds/malicious-url-scanner)
    * [File Malware Scanner
        
        File Virus Checker](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/file-malware-scanner)
    * [Data Breach Search
        
        Leaked Data Search Engine](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/data-breach-search-engine)
    * [Leaked Email Checker
        
        Search Leaked Emails](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/data-breach-lookup/leaked-email-checker)
    * [Leaked Password Checker
        
        Search Leaked Passwords](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/data-breach-lookup/password-leak-check)
    * [Leaked Username Checker
        
        Search Compromised Usernames](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/data-breach-lookup/compromised-usernames)
    * [Cyberthreat Intelligence
        
        Identify Advanced Cyberthreats](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/cyberthreat-intelligence-map)
    * [Threat Intelligence Feeds
        
        Real-Time Threat Feeds](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/threat-intelligence-feed-api)
    * [Dark Web Monitoring
        
        Track Dark Web Leaks](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/dark-web-monitoring-api)
    * [URL Scanning API
        
        Link Scanning Documentation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/malicious-url-scanner-api/overview)
    * [Virus Scanning API
        
        File Scanning Documentation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/malware-file-scanner-api/overview)
* [ ]  Solutions
    * [Ecommerce Fraud
        
        Securely Process Payments](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/ecommerce-fraud-prevention)
    * [Address Verification
        
        Verify Physical Addresses](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/address-verification)
    * [User Validation
        
        Verify Identities with Precision](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/user-application-screening)
    * [Account Takeover (ATO)
        
        Detect Suspicious Logins](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/account-takeover-credential-stuffing-fraud-prevention)
    * [Bot Protection
        
        Detect Automated Bots](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/bot-protection-mitigation)
    * [Chargeback Prevention
        
        Detect Fraudulent Chargebacks](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/chargeback-fraud-prevention)
    * [Prevent Sign Up Fraud
        
        New Account Opening Screening](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/prevent-fake-registration-fraud)
    * [Invalid Traffic (IVT)
        
        Prevent Ad Fraud](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/solutions/invalid-traffic-detection)
    * [Fraud Detection API
        
        Risk Scoring API Documentation](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/overview)
* [ ]  Fraud Detection Tools
    * [Bot Detection
        
        Block Bad Bots](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/bot-detection)
    * [Block Proxies
        
        Detect Proxies & Bots](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/block-proxies)
    * [Block Disposable Emails
        
        Prevent Bad Users](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/block-disposable-emails)
    * [Click Fraud Prevention
        
        Monitor Fraudulent Traffic](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/click-fraud-prevention)
    * [Prevent Affiliate Fraud
        
        Affiliate Network Fraud Detection](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/prevent-affiliate-ad-fraud)
    * [Detect Mobile App Fraud
        
        Identify Mobile Emulators & Bots](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/detect-mobile-app-install-fraud)
    * [Fake & Duplicate Accounts
        
        Stop Fake Accounts](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/duplicate-fake-account-detection)
    * [Fraud Fusion™
        
        Fraud Detection Consortium](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/features/fraud-fusion)
    * [Transaction Risk Scoring API
        
        Verify Payments in Real-Time](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/documentation/proxy-detection-api/transaction-scoring)

Privacy Policy
==============

_Last Revised June 25, 2024_  
**IPQualityScore (IPQS) values your privacy and is fully compliant with GDPR, CCPA, VCDPA, and similar regulations. All data shared with IPQualityScore (IPQS) API endpoints is confidential and securely processed. Please also review our [Data Processing Agreement](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/data-processing-agreement) for more details.**

IPQualityScore (IPQS) Privacy Policy Overview
---------------------------------------------

This Privacy Policy document outlines the privacy measures of IPQualityScore, LLC (referred to as "IPQualityScore", "IPQS", "we", or "us"), in relation to the IPQualityScore.com website (the "Website") and any features, products, and online services (referred to as "services") provided by IPQualityScore. IPQualityScore values the privacy of our visitors and users. This Privacy Policy details the types of data and information that we collect and how we safeguard this data.

Our Services That Process Data
------------------------------

IPQualityScore's primary service is focused on fraud detection and prevention. We may use data related to you to analyze transactions, registrations, clicks, and other user behavior to determine if the intent is malicious or fraudulent. IPQualityScore's machine learning algorithms and data processing mechanisms are designed with this privacy framework in mind to prevent data leakage and protect your rights to privacy.

Web Server Log Files
--------------------

Like most web sites, IPQualityScore makes use of log files through our web server. This data includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and timestamps, referring & exit pages, and clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. Each of these data points is not personally identifiable on its own.

Scripts, Cookies, and Web Beacons
---------------------------------

IPQualityScore may use cookies, pixel tags, embedded scripts, web beacons and similar technologies to store information about visitor preferences, record user behavior and actions, customize services based on the visitor's browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. Users with "Do Not Track" enabled will be respected with limited data tracking.

Information & Data Collection
-----------------------------

**Personal Information**: information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable individual, including: name, unique identifier (such as account ID), email address, physical address, telephone number, credit card information, geolocation, and IP address. If you submit any Personal Information relating to other people to us or to our service providers in connection with our services, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Non-Personal Information**: any information that does not directly reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an identifiable individual. This might include pseudonymous identifiers and information, device information, non-precise geolocation, information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies, and web server log files to track trends, administer the Website, track user movement, and gather demographic information.

IPQualityScore does not collect more information than is necessary to provide accurate fraud detection services.

Data Sharing & Data Processing
------------------------------

Clients using our service may provide IPQualityScore with transactional information, which may include IP addresses, email addresses, billing details, phone numbers, and similar user data. This information is securely processed through our services to detect behavioral intent and analyze the risk profile of transactions, users, and similar events. This data is used to identify patterns of fraud within our system and improve your account's personal machine learning algorithms.

IPQualityScore does not sell your personal data or the personal data of your end users. Any data shared with IPQualityScore will be confidential, securely processed, and maintained in-line with industry security standards. Your account's contact details may be shared with CRMs and marketing platforms which meet our standards for adequate security techniques and data processing safeguards.

This safeguards within this section shall provide IPQualityScore the right to share necessary data with third parties for any false-positive reports submitted through our feedback forms to [unblock an IP address](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/unblock-ip-address) , [report a false-positive](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/report-false-positive) , or [register an IP address](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/register-ip-address-business-organization) . This data may be shared with third parties to improve accuracy.

Data Processing Agreement
-------------------------

Please review our full [Data Processing Agreement](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/data-processing-agreement) for more details on how we handle personal data while respecting relevant privacy laws including the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA).

Data Security
-------------

IPQualityScore takes reasonable measures to protect all data collected from unauthorized access, breaches, loss, manipulation, falsification, destruction or unauthorized disclosure.

Your Privacy Rights & Access to Information
-------------------------------------------

You have the right to request access to any personal information we may have collected for you. IPQualityScore can provide a copy of your stored personal data. In order to comply with your request, we may ask you to verify your identity. Please contact us at [Support@IPQualityScore.com](mailto:S%75p%70or%74@IP%51uality%53c%6Fre%2Ecom) to submit a personal information request.

Information Correction & Deletion
---------------------------------

If you believe that the information we have recorded about you is incorrect, you are welcome to contact us so we can update it and keep your data accurate. You also have the right to request that we delete any information about you. In order to comply with your request, we may ask you to verify your identity. Please contact us at [Support@IPQualityScore.com](mailto:S%75p%70or%74@IP%51uality%53c%6Fre%2Ecom) to submit an information deletion request.

CCPA Opt-Out — "Do Not Sell Or Share My Personal Information"
-------------------------------------------------------------

Privacy laws, such as the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) or the Virginia Consumer Data Privacy Act (VCDPA), afford residents of some states the right to opt out of the sale or sharing of personal information, defined in a way that may include the transfer and sharing of data to third parties to predict your preferences or interests to personalize ads for you on those third party platforms.

In order to comply with your "do not share" request, we may ask you to verify your identity. Please contact us at [Support@IPQualityScore.com](mailto:S%75p%70or%74@IP%51uality%53c%6Fre%2Ecom) to submit your request or [contact us](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/contact-us) using our support form.

Data Compliance Officer
-----------------------

Should you have any questions related to your privacy or would like to speak with our Data Compliance Officer, please use the contact information below.  
  
ATTN: Data Compliance Officer  
IPQualityScore LLC  
PO Box 19052  
Las Vegas, Nevada 89132  
USA  

Summary
-------

IPQualityScore takes every precaution to safeguard your data. We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time as we constantly improve our policies.

If you require more details or have any questions concerning our Privacy Policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://www.ipqualityscore.com/contact-us).

Ready to eliminate fraud?
-------------------------

### Start fighting fraud now with 5,000 Free Lookups!

We're happy to answer any questions or concerns. Chat with our fraud detection experts any day of the week.

### Call us at: [(800) 713-2618](tel:8007132618)

### Copyright © 2011 - 2024 IPQualityScore LLC

### Products & Tools

### Company

* * *

#### **All Systems Operational**
